<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Share a memory of a holiday. Where was it, who went, what happened…?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 60 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Three years ago, I travelled with my friends's group in Easthern Europe. More precisely, in Romenia, Hungaria and Serbia.</p>
                <p>First, we arrived in Belgrad which is the capital city of Serbia. It's a strange city... we didn't feel really safe there. Moreover, there were some buildings destroyed by the war yet. But, we had good times.</p>
                <p>Next, we had taken the train to a city in Romenia before to take an other train that take us to a small village. There, we helped poeple and farmers during one week. It was good because we met people and it's always nice to help when we can.</p>
                <p>Finally, we went to Budapest that is one of the better cities that I saw in my life. It's a wonderful city. It was a gread travel for everyone in my friends's group.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
