<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="23" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>You attended an event. Write an article for your blog.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Two days ago i attended to a football match, this match maybe you have heard about it. This football match was Liverpool from</p>
                <p>England aigainst Dortmund from Germany in quarter final from europa chamions league.</p>
                <p>The two teams were very good and it was really exited game beacause all fans from each country were excited for the qualification of their team.</p>
                <p>As you know in europa champions league every team have to play one match out and there is one more at home. The game i am talking about is the return match which were played at Liverpool. The first game in Germany was 2-2 and for that reason Liverpool has pression of wining the second match.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This was an interessting and excited football game i have never seen in my life. Dortmund scored directly after about 10minutes and Liverpool fans were dispointed. After 40minutes the score was 1-3 and every body thinks that it was finished for Liverpool but at the end Liverpool won 4-5.</p>
                <p>we hope to see how goes Liverpool at the semi final</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
