<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>If I had 1 million euros, first, I would spend a few weeks to realise it and I would wait full time to be enough ready to do whatever with it. Wait to be a the right road of my life. Certainely, I wouldn't tell it my friends, my family maybe.</p>
                <p>Majority of poeple would say, yeah I'll go on holidays at the paradise with beautiful sun, beach, ocean, ... You imagine that! The men would buy a crazy car, girls would go shopping days  and days.</p>
                <p>No no, you know, it's not for me. So many poeple in the world stay without water or food. I grew in a certain comfort, as everyone and it's true than you'll actually do everything to keep it in your life. The problem is that haven't any limit. I might not live in an extreme comfort knowing the rest of the world can't live with the minimum.</p>
                <p>It's a problem for long time and the solutions are not so simple. However, I advocate that it would be very better if people like me, you, us with enought or too much comfort  would share more with the other.</p>
                <p>This problem is so intricate, I have actually nothing solution but, with so many money, I would thought until I find out a way not-too-bad to remiade at this. Every people with this money might do beautiful actions for the world and the unacceptable differences.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
