<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="19" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the best book you've ever read and why?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The best book I've read! What a difficult question.</p>
                <p>I think it's &quot;Lakeshore Christmas&quot;. It's a book of Susan Wiggs.</p>
                <p>It's a very interesting book for me because it speaks of a lot of subjects that I love: books, love, shy, interest, culture, surpassing oneself and so on. It's a book who's really easy to read, you don't need a extrem concentration to understand (Even so, it isn't a book for idiot of course!)</p>
                <p>The main character is a librarian in the United States and she must find a solution to preserve the library where she works. Because this library must be supported, and the supportman just died. She will be helped by a person she dislike very hard. This &quot;angel&quot; will make a big campaign to help her.</p>
                <p>But, in a other part of the story, it's also about the life of this person who helped the main character. And of course, here it's the librarian who help this man.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
