<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>You attended an event. Write an article for your blog.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Last night i went to an event called &quot;Spring Tech Edition&quot; organised by the Kot &amp;amp; Mix which rassembled many techno Dj's.</p>
                <p>The price was as low as 3 euros even though they had booked some pretty famous artists.</p>
                <p>Let me tell you, the music was so great that i found it hard to even go out for a minute to get some fresh air. The sound quality was flawless, there were great visuals, the place was nice and overall, everything was well organised.</p>
                <p>Unfortunately, there was not as many people as the Kot &amp;amp; Mix crew predicted, my guess is that the bad weather was a turn off for some of them. Nonetheless i'm sure everyone, from the dj's to the people dancing had a great time there.</p>
                <p>I do hope that the Kot &amp;amp; Mix crew planned to throw more parties like this one because it's a great step back from the mainstream scene and a way to enjoy lesser known artist's music.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
