<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="de"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>If I had 1 million euros I would do a lot of things with it. Frirst, I would probably think about all those things I could buy or do for myself such as buy a big house, go on holidays, buy clothes, a car, a boat and so on. But in a second time, I would of course think deeper and realize that keeping 1 million euros just for myself and my little happiness would be really selfish.</p>
                <p>Due to this reflexion, I would give a part of this fortune to poor countries, poor families and children; people who will need this money much more than me. Also, I would propably ground a foundation who cares about women and their children who has to run away from war or violent husband or father all around the world. I would like this foundation to protect these people and to offer them a place where they can sleep, eat, learn in schools, have drugs and medical help.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
