<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="27" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the best book you've ever read and why?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I don't read that much, but the last book I remember have read is ''Marriage'' I really don't remember the name of the autor but the history was interesting. The book was talking about a young lady with studies already donne; she was working already. I think  she had her own Business. She was a lawyer, but celebrity's lawyor. Hers parents does't understqnd why she chose those specialisation, but they were happy for they daugther succes, she was known by all Hollywood's celebrities and have won a lots and big causes defending celebrities. In the other hand she had a boyfriend yong lawyer too but not working with celebrities but with other causes with 'popular' people. He were once married so have one kid. They were verry independent leaving each other in they own home. its was not that easy but they like a lot each other compagnie...</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
