<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="19" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the best book you've ever read and why?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The best book i've ever read is &quot; Human &quot; by Yann Arthus Bertrand. This book speak about nature, history, the earth, the oceans, the animals and for sur the environement. Why this is the best book i've ever read ? Because i think, this is very important for our population to make some efforts for the planet. We must be careful with the ecology, we must be prudent with a lot differnts things like the cars, the protection of animals. The polution is a problem for the health. A lot of people dead every year because of that. The demography is important in 2016 and it will be dangerous if the demography continues like that. We 've got a lot of solutions to make the world better, for example, reduce the density in a lot of great town as Paris, London.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
