<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the best book you've ever read and why?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The best book I have ever read is &quot;Oscar and the pink lady&quot; by Eric Emmanuel Schmitt. I choose this one because, I found it very interesting and very very emotional. I was 11 or 12 when I first read this book who talks about a little boy who has got cancer and he is about to dead and a old lady helps him to enjoy his last days on earth. This book touch me and I have already read it 2-3 times, it helps you to realise that life is beautiful and worth to live, that millions of people are poor and sick all around the world and we have to be thankful for all we have and when you are 12 and you read this book I can say that you never forget the story of Oscar. This book is a less for life which teach us we have to enjoy every moment in our life no matter what happens. Carpe diem.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
