<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the best book you've ever read and why?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>the best book I've ever read is called &quot;la formle de Dieu&quot; written by jozé rodriguez dos santos. the purpose of this book is to show, by the way of physics and quantum mechanic, that the whole universe would have been created by an intelligent being. What attracted me a lot is the fact that the whole scientific content is empiricaly founded or defended by number of scientist. So it me makes my reading more interesting due to all implication about the human life that are revealed in this book. But it's also because of the author who makes understandable something witch is occult for a lot of poeple : the quantum mechanic. furthermore it is romanced, so there is more tan the scientific content that makes me keep reading whitout thinking that it was to heavy for me.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
