<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The first question is: How can i get 1 million euros? Dealing drugs? Get a offshore account? Mmmh maybe get married with an old rich wife? But anyway.. That's not the point! If i had one million euros, i will be first really really happy! But attention! I've to keep my mind cold! I must do a goed use of this money! When you beome rich, the next step is getting richer... So i think that i will buy a lot of sure actions in Wall street and make sure that they don't increase... Next step, i must engage an accountant to be sure that i won't spend my money in one day. So i would entoure myself with professionals, and make my fortune grown. and after that when i will be sure that i don't have to work for the rest of my life, i would give a lot of money to my parents and my brothers (before i must be perfectly sure that that they will do a good use of this money too). i would give a lot of money to a lot to charity. And at the end, buying a lot of useless to have the impress that my new life is better than the last.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
