<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>You attended an event. Write an article for your blog.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Hi ladies and gentlemen!! Last night I was in Brussel at the Mirano club. You know about it, it's a fancy place where young ladies with short dress like to dance. The bar was pretty big and the red light gave a nice atmospher. Drinking was expensive but they had good cocktails. It's not the kind of club where I like to go but Nekfeu, the famous french rap artist, attempt to do a showcase here!!! I waited for three hours before he came. But when he came, whaaa it was amazing!! He was on fire!! He arrived on the stage with all his team and they began to poured champagne on all the public!! Everybody was crazy and screaming the lyrics of his songs. It was short, he only did a few songs but the last one was so great !!! I had one of the best night of my life.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
