<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="19" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>If I had I million euros, I would like to make a big trip all aroud the world. Discovering a lot of countrys and differents types of cultures. Going first on South-Africa, then in the persian golf. Visit India and try to understand the poperty in taht land. I would like to go than in China , to visit the big city , in Thailand and Taiwan, then going to eat sushi's in Japan. Than gooing on South America , especially to Peru , to see MAchu Pichu and the formidable culture of the Inca's. The cheeling on a white beach in the caraibes. Then visit North America , the big city's in Canada and in the USA. After, why not choosing a destination that I particulary like during my long trip alla around the world and make in that place my home?</p>
                <p>I think have money is fine, but what is still more great is visiting the world!!!!</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
