<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the best book you've ever read and why?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>One of the best books I have ever read, was Harry Potter. Al the seven books are amazing, I still read them sometimes.</p>
                <p>I think the autor of Harry Potter has created a fantastic new world, her imagination is incredible. These stories are a great way to relax, and put your problems away for a moment.</p>
                <p>When I was little, my mom read a chapter every night for me and my brothers. This books are also something nostalgiq, and I don't think I am the only person who sees the stories of Harry Potter as a part of their childhood.</p>
                <p>But the amazing thing is that these books are also for adults, I think their is no age for them.</p>
                <p>Harry Potter will stay an important story for the next generations, it has become a part of our culture.</p>
                <p>This is why Harry Potter is one of my favorite books, and I don't think I am the only person that loves it.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
