<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I think it's right to say that studying abroad is a compulsary part of the education. We are living in a world where all is more and more open to others civilisations and others countries. So if you you leave your country to study in another country, after or during your studies, during 6 month or a year, you'll have a considerable advantage to begin your career path.</p>
                <p>Moreover, I think that studying abroad can bring you a lot of things for your personal development. First, you will dicover new civilisations and new ways of living and working. Furthermore, ou can learn new marketing and financial dispositions and you have also a bigger baggage for beginning working.</p>
                <p>To conclude, I think that it's a good choice to propose to students to do a part of their studies abroad and that would be continued.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
