<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Studying Business Ingeneering, I will be on the Job market in two years and therefore I am asking my self about what kind of job I will look for : An enjoyable one or would I prefer a bigger wage?</p>
                <p>Of course the best option would be both making money and having an simpathetic job. I truly think that those kinds of jobs exist. There are maybe hard to find but life is long enought to find it.</p>
                <p>Yet ending university I will have to find a job quickly and therefore it will be hard to directly find my dream job. I think that a that moment I will choose the job that will makes my learned what I like most. At that time the most important thing will be the atmosphere, how I am feeling.</p>
                <p>Then after having learned new things, after having grew my network, I will have enought knowledge to find and to get the job that feet best to me. There the salary will have a way bigger impact on my choice because I want to enjoy life without having &quot;money-fences&quot;.</p>
                <p>To conclude both salary and the job feeling are important for me. And therefore my future job will be a great mixt between those 2 sides.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
