<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>A journey is always an adventure! In an adventure you can experiment a lot of things, these things would allow you to grow up and dependly on what you done abroad it would certainly be a great experience for your life.</p>
                <p>First, studying aboard can porvide you to learn a other language then your mother tongue. When you live in a country wich you don't speak the language of, you must communicate and adapt for expressing your needs or point of view. For doing that you are obligated to learn it beaucuse you are bathed in it.</p>
                <p>Second, studying what you like in an other country is a good manier for knowing how your favorite science is teached in the opposit part of the globe. You can in the same time meet friends, fall in love and making things you never thought of because the atmosphere of an Erasmus are completely different from the mood you have in your own country.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
