<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="25" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Travelling, a life's experience</p>
                <p>To open mind of young peole, visiting other countries ans discover new cultures is a good way. In making compulsory studying abroad, first it will force people to go above the language barrier and so leran a new one. It will be an advantage in their future professional career.</p>
                <p>Secondly, by meeting new people they will be more tolerant and capable to understand several different traditions. They will face different laws and way of living and will must conforme to it in their new land. By making friends with other foreign students, they will make connexions and friendships around the world.</p>
                <p>To conclude, travelling is the best way to become a real man and open the mind to the entire world.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
