<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I really want to study abroad but I don't think forcing people to do it is a good idea. According to me, this must be a personnel decision. If somebody chooses to do such a projet, he will be more motivated to do it.</p>
                <p>Moreover, this might be hard for some people to go living some times far from them friends and family. These people might not enjoy the experience and benefit from it. This could be worse than anything else.</p>
                <p>Furthermore, study abroad costs money: you have to find an appartement, buying furniture, sometime the cost of living in the host country is also higher, etc. Who gonna paid for this? Is it the student or his parents who could perhaps not afford? Or is it a new hole in the state budget? I really think money should be invested in a better place to improve education or to help people in an other way.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
