<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="nl"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I don't think studying abroad is a must do. But it can learn you to have a better knowledge about an other language. I would love to study in England, because I love speaking english and it would help me to improve my english and have a better accent. Nowadays, a lot of youngsters go abroad after their secondary education and before university to learn english or an other language. I think it's a great experience, you learn to live with other habits. But I also think the youngsters aren't there to work. I think studying abroad when you are in the higher education is a good deal : you have to work and you learn a second language. I would love to do an Erasmus abroad, and especially in  England. But I also know that for communication studies, Belgiums universities are high rated, so it would be stupid to go to an other university that has not the same level as ours and that is certainly more expensive.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
