<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="22" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="az"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What advice would you give to help improve the environment?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>One of the biggest problematic issues that the humanity faced today is the preserving of the environment. This issue disturb both economically, and physically.</p>
                <p>I can completely agree with a Canadian social activist Naomi Klein, that in order to save the planet the drastic measures should be realised. From my point of view, these measures will allow to humanity to understand how it is important to change our lifestyle in favor of the planet. The politicians should take into consideration that all the society must be engaged in resolving of that crucial question.</p>
                <p>In the interest of changing the society, some social issues should be changed, for instance, the education. The futur engineers should be capable to products kind of technologes that will allow to decrease the amount of pollution, and save the green spaces as much as it is possible.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
