<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I think study abroad is very important for the education. Students can discover a whole new culture and meet people all over the world.</p>
                <p>But even more, it can help students to learn a different language and to have clases en that new language. This is really interresting because they can use that language later for their jobs.</p>
                <p>And most of all, study abroad gives experiences. I personnaly went in Canada for an exchange program and it gave me a lot of experiences. I could learn that the culture is very different from ours, even if it is still an occidental counrty, I also learned the language very well and not to be shy when I try to talk english.</p>
                <p>Finally I really think study abroad should be a compulsory part of the eductaion because it brings experiences, knowledge and you meet a lot of people. This is an amazing time when you study abroad.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
