<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I think it is more important to have a job that you love. An enjoyable job that make you happy and contented. If you're feeling good in your mind and soul, you won't need to have lots of money. The necessary will be enough. You won't need to go on holidays to far away and sunny places, or to go to the spa or the restaurant often because your everyday world and life will fulfill these needs of well-being and wellness. Furthermore, a person that enjoys its job is going to do it better that someone that doesn't enjoy it.</p>
                <p>I think that getting money for a job that makes you feel unfulfilled is some kind of dangerous for your health. Cases of burn-out and depression doesn't come from nowhere, and they're highly bonded with a feeling of overwork and mental fatigue. These come when a person do a job that she doesn't enjoy, even if she gets lots of money for it. Going on holiday won't resolve the problem, it could even getting it worse.</p>
                <p>So I think that everyone should choose a job that he loves, regarding to the heart and not the wallet. Cause it's our heart that makes us live.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
