<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="23" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The study abroad is first of all a choice</p>
                <p>In my opinion, study abroad should remain a choice.</p>
                <p>Admittedly, studying in a foreigner country is potentially very beneficial because this kind of study puts the person in good predisposition in order to imporve their skill in another language or to become more able to handle various situations.</p>
                <p>However, making it compulsory would create several problems : some people can't afford to be &quot;expatriated&quot; or just don't want to. This could be caused by financial, familial issues or they don't have the right temperament to handle such a journey.</p>
                <p>Taking this in consideration, study abroad should be more encouraged but still be a way that a student could have the choice to take or not.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
