<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="37" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="lower-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Imagine your life in 10 years time. What will it look like?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 60 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>In ten years, my children will be all adulte and i will have more free time. I will hope to speak very well English langage. I imagine that i will must to learn a lot of. I would like to live in England or in Canada for to improve my stress. I will love to visite the wonderfull landscapes in Canada.</p>
                <p>In ten years, i will have to buy my big house with a lovely garden. There will be a big living home, a modern kitchen, five bedrooms, tree bathroom and a long terrasse with a heatead swimming pool inside. Maybe, i will see a good sunset erery day if my house is near the beach.</p>
                <p>In ten years, i will be a manager in my company. I will work hard fot that. My company will be leader in pieces of cars (ABS). It will grow in many country in the world.</p>
                <p>In ten years, i will travel once every month in the country. I will visit the monuments, museums, big bridges and i will discover each culture.</p>
                <p>Finaly, i will be very happy in ten years.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
