<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="44" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I never really think about this, but If I had 1 million euros, I will first, give 10 pourcents to an association. I will look on the net to search one structure that help people as the resto du coeur but I will prefered to find one that is less mediatic and that has very difficulties to found money.</p>
                <p>Then I will spoil me and my family. I will use some of that money to buy a big kitchen to cook as a profesional to offer to my husban that loves to create nice meal. A huge dressing room for my daughter and a shooping credit card of 25000 euros. A pool in a veranda that can be heated in winter and open roof during summer. For my son a little loft.</p>
                <p>As travel agent I already see a lot of the world but to spoil me, I will organise a wonderful trip in soutn America wich is the continent I never visit.</p>
                <p>But It will never happen!</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
