<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="28" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="primary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the best book you've ever read and why?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The best book i ever read was treasure Island from Robert Louis Stevenson.</p>
                <p>There is now sixteen years ago. It was the first book who gave me pleasure to read. My french teacher forced me to chose a book for a work (the objectif was to read a book and make a text on it to give others want to read it) and i was not really interested in this but, after fews pages, it was a great discovery.</p>
                <p>First of all, i discovered how a book offers you more possibilities than films to create your own world and characters. No matter how the author could describe things, you can always imagine them as you want.</p>
                <p>The second point i discovered is the pirate world, The way they live and think.This stylish and highly regulated side but without concessions seduced me.</p>
                <p>Since this moment, i read a lot and especially books on stories of pirates.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
