<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="58" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I should share a big part of this money with my children, helping them to pay their home an offer them nice holidays.</p>
                <p>I should travel with my husband all over the world and offer the opportunity to my grand childrens to visit New York. I should go back to Ecuador to visit my friend {name} who was a exchange student during one year in our family, ten years ago but I shoud not stop to work because I have a guesthome and I like to welcome people from evrywhere in the world.</p>
                <p>Because, I like good food, I should go to reputaded restaurants to taste and discover a another way of gastronomy. After thinking to me and my family, I should help people in necessity in my municipality. I also certainely help artists, buying them some art pieces because I like art but never have enough money to buy anything or I know that it's not easy for the artist to live with their own art passion.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
