<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="73" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>You attended an event. Write an article for your blog.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I attended a football match beetween real madrid and chelsea.</p>
                <p>These competitors are famous, and one of them could be the best</p>
                <p>in the word.</p>
                <p>During the first game, the two teams were equal, half of the time</p>
                <p>real madrid was very offensive, then it was chelsea.</p>
                <p>At the start of the second game, it was the same, some times</p>
                <p>chelsea was very offensive, the it was the turn of real madrid.</p>
                <p>The two teams were very excellent, and it was impossible to choose</p>
                <p>the better. Each goal keeper was busy to stop the balls, each player did his best.   ,,,, but the score was always the same, zero/zero,</p>
                <p>no difference at all, the english public was enthousiastic, the spanish</p>
                <p>public was the same;</p>
                <p>it was fantastic to attend a match beetween two excellent teams,</p>
                <p>It was impossible to say and to choose which team is the best,</p>
                <p>Finally  each one was a champion for two reasons, excellent competitor</p>
                <p>and each player was fair, it was a fair play game beetween two</p>
                <p>champion competitors</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
