<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="52" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The house of happiness</p>
                <p>I'm only fifty-two years old but I sometimes think about the old age. When I see old people who can't stay any more alone at home, I'm sad. I know some of them in my circle. Their children are obliged to put them in an old people's home. They would prefer to stay with their family and friends.</p>
                <p>If I won one million euros, here's what I would do: I would buy a piece of land and I would build a comfortable house with some flats. Every flat would contain a bedroom, a bathroom and a sitting room.</p>
                <p>In this building, there would be also rooms for the community life as a kitchen, a living-room, a sitting-room with a television, a terrace and a garden. Many people like a cook, a nurse, a gardener and others would be in charge of the elderly people and would live among them with their family.</p>
                <p>So these people would never be alone and would live happy.</p>
                <p>One day, when I'll be old, I would seize the opportunity to live like them in my house of happiness.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
