<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="32" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The most important is definitely an enjoyable job...but a good salary can make it even more enjoyable! We spend a major part of our life working so feeling happy with his job is very important. There will always be more difficult moments in our lifes but knowing why we wake up every morning will make it easier to go through these harder moments. On the orther hand, earning a good salary is always nice and can give you more motivation...but not for a long time if you don't like enough your job. Indeed, feeling some fear every sunday evening and every morning of the week gives you a huge risk of depression or even burnout!</p>
                <p>Money can buy lots of things and can gives you some joy but happiness is the best way of enjoying life and staying healthy!</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
