<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="18" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="lower-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>In my opinion, study abroad is very important for the education. Nowadays, it's expensive to study abroad so if it's compulsory, maybe the governement would make it more affordable. Plus, in school we have only five hours of'English lessons which is not enough! At least you're immersed, it's impossible to get ou of school bilingual. Study abroad would make the young more independant, they would learn and see another culture and they would considerably improve their second language. Furthermore, more and more young people are lazy or too confortable in their routine to go study abroad by themselve but I think it's an experience which would do them good. In conclusion, study abroad should be a compulsory part of education, even if it's for a few days because the young could see something else and maybe it would make them study and learn better.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
