<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="19" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I don't think it should be compulsory because some students may not enjoy going abroad. We cannot impose such a thing to someone. But I think that the opportunity should be offered to everyone. Maybe at the last year of high school, we could propose to students to go 6 months abroad to finish their cursus. Or schools could also work with organisation such as WEP to encourage students to go abroad. We should also give scholarship to every students who desire to go abroad because it is very expensive and not everyone can have a scholarship nowadays so by giving them more easily, more students would go abroad. Belgian schools should develop a kind of network with other schools in other countries, so the exchange would be easier. Studying abroad have a lot of advantages, it is a real asset in a life. We definitely should invest in that perspective.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
