<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="29" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>From my point of view and my personnal experience, study abroad should be a compulsory part of education.</p>
                <p>I went abroad around 18 years old, during 1 month in the USA to improve my english and it was such a great experience: I improved my english, i discovered a new country/culture and i met new peoples from all around the world. Moreover I went there by my self so it's aso a great personnal challenge.</p>
                <p>Then 2 years later, I made an internship in London for 4 months, amazing experience too.</p>
                <p>And finally I did an Erasmus semester in London. Thoses 6 months in London were amazing: I was living a dream by living in my favourite city, always doing something et discovering new things everyday and meeting people.</p>
                <p>Those 3 experiences abroad were my choice, never in highschool/upgrade studies they suggest us to go abroad.</p>
                <p>But as french, the english courses in collegre, high school are not pushed and I really imporved my english by going abroad.</p>
                <p>So I think that the school need to propose a time abroad (from 2 weeks to severals months) to let students have this opportunity.</p>
                <p>Of course we need to care in consideration also the financial part...find a way that help also the one who have less revenue to have this experience, to enjoy it.</p>
                <p>It was the best experience i eved had, and if one day I have a child, i would like him to have this opportunity!</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
