<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="66" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>In my point of view, it 's very more important to have an enjoyable job, a job which you feel beter with.</p>
                <p>Every morning, when you wake-up, you know that you will be usefull . It is easier to be blossomed in a job that fit you.</p>
                <p>Indeed, it is important to make money too, But, generaly, when you are satisfied with your work, you are with your wage; Your satisfaction can make your relatives happy,. Your health will surely  be improved.; and for your mental, it is well known that we must keep keen . Some people are going to tell you the contrary, but everybody knows that money doesn't make happyness, but A good job gives us health..</p>
                <p>However, I think that money and an enjoyable job must be balanced: because if you eventualy suffer from a lack of money, it will be more diffucult to keep happyness at home and overall, to give your family a good education.</p>
                <p/>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
