<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="43" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What advice would you give to help improve the environment?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Well, that's a very good topic also this one is not so abvious to reply.</p>
                <p>But on my level, I can tell you that I educate my daughters to use only water they need. For example to stop the water when they brush their teeth or when they use the saop for a shower.</p>
                <p>On my side, I sort out the paper and carton boxes , all plastics recycling things and the rest of food. By talking about food, I try to avoid waste.</p>
                <p>As I am the purchaser, I mean the person in my familly who buy goods, I plan in my head all the meals I will prepare for the forthcoming week.</p>
                <p>By this way, I know excactely what I have to buy. That's avoid compulsif purchasing behaviour which lead to wastes.</p>
                <p>An other action I try to follow is &quot;no car &quot; during the week-end. It's better for health and for the wallet.</p>
                <p>I know that I could modify my behaviour to improve the environment by stopping my hollidays with flights ( big pollution way) but I can not having all the qualities ......</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
