<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="24" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I don't think it should be an obligation to leave our country to another one, we've got all what we need to learn a foreign language. When I was in High School, we learned some experiences did by several scientists, and those were in English; I did love that.</p>
                <p>However, It will be beneficial to spend some weeks in a country where the spoken mother tongue is the tongue we want to learn. I would like to go in England for instance, that would be awesome.</p>
                <p>Actually, I like to think that my English level is basic, and I know if I go in an other country, where the people who speak english, my English level would be will increase.</p>
                <p>To conclude, Leave our country for another one to increase our language level should be advise, but not compulsory.</p>
                <p>Thank you!</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
