<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What advice would you give to help improve the environment?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The first advice I would give is to never ever throw any garbage in the nature because even one plastic bottle abandoned in the forest is very disgusting and harmful to the environment.</p>
                <p>The second advice would be to separate the papers from plastic in your bin. That way, trashes can be recycled an get a second life. Otherwise they will be burned and that's going to spread out a very toxic smoke which is hardocre for the environment.</p>
                <p>And finally, the third and last advice is to try to take a look at the labels of the product you buy to see if they come from your country or if they have been imported from far away. I think that if everybody paid attention to buy local product in priority it would be helpful to the environment because one merchant ship is way more polluting than a lot of cars.</p>
                <p>And voilà !</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
