<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="37" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I fully agree with this proposition.  I didn't have the opportunity to study abroad after High School or Univerity but I think it 's really a very interesting experience.  There are many benefits: learn a language  morequickly, increase the skills to speak  with more insurance, hear the correct pronunciation and also develop our networking abroad.  For my job,I was in CERAN last year durong a week and my progess were awersome just because I spoke in Englis all the day! The immersion allows also to &quot;think&quot; in the new language. So if the Education could oranise one year aobraod for all students, it will we really a chance for them. But be carefful, financing this project is surely an important challenge! If study abroad becomes an &quot;obligation&quot;, every student should have the possibility to do it with the same opportunities!</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
