<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="25" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What advice would you give to help improve the environment?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Environment is a critical concern for the future of mankind. An important part of our economy and sustain depends on the environment (forestry, fishery, agriculture, medicine ...) and it is our duty to protect it.</p>
                <p>We should, for example, consider more seriously the use of biological control as a good mean to reduce the populations of harmful insects in the crops. It won't only lead to the decrease of pest population but will avoid soil contamination by utilization of hazardous pesticides.</p>
                <p>Furthermore, it is essential to explain why it is important to protect the environment. The parents and teachers should work on it with the children.</p>
                <p>Education is a fundamental key.</p>
                <p>Moreover, the recycling process allows the reuse of items as raw material for the production of new items in order to save natural ressources.</p>
                <p>Eventually, it's good to remember that the great changes in society can be operated by politics. They have a role to play in this concern.</p>
                <p>We should'nt forget that money we make with industries won't buy another planet !</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
