<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="25" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Eating a balanced diet is the most important factor for a healthy life. Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>There are several factors that contribute to a healthy life. Among them, we can think about balanced diet, sport, healty behaviors (no drug consumption for example). We could organise these factors as &quot;personnal factors&quot;, as these behaviors depend on one's will.</p>
                <p>But, are there others contribution to an healthy life? We could analyse the environnement where the subject lives. The air quality, the water sanity, the noise, all of these factors will have an impact on the life of a person. These are &quot;external factors&quot;, that do not depend on the subject's will.</p>
                <p>A smart reader may infer that a personnal factor of a person can be an external factor of another: the smoke of someone decreases the quality of the air repired by another person, as a dummy example.</p>
                <p>To answer the question, it is difficult to guess what is the most important factor. First, we just saw that a factor for someone is, in fact, another factor for someone else: it is thus difficult to isolate a factor.</p>
                <p>Second, we must be able to measure a magnitude of the impact of a factor on the healthyness of the life. The noise generated by an airport will impact more people living close to the airport and badly affect their quality of life but, for people living in calm suburbs, the most important factor might be the diet.</p>
                <p>We can quickly sum up our point stating that there is no thing such as &quot;most important factor&quot; because that depends on the studied subject and its environnement. The notion is not universal. But we can regroup people in population affected the same way by a same kind of factor.</p>
                <p>That indicates us that, for example, a government that would build a program exclusively on balanced diet will not increase the quality of life of the whole population and would be wise studying all the factors, either personnal and external.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
