<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="26" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the impact of social networks on relationships?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>There are two side of social netwoks in a relationship</p>
                <p>The first is to be able to speak with your girlfriend or boyfriend whenever you want and whenever they are. For exemple I live in Belgium for the moment but my girlfriend is in Canada for an intership.Thanks to social networks like facebook, skype or hangout we are able to speak to each other on a daily basis. It helps us to miss each other less.</p>
                <p>The second side of social network is really bad for a relationship. There is a risk to spy on your love one, try to know with who she or he is talking to. The other bad thing about it, it's really time consuming. You see some couple in a restaurent stare at their phone for 10 minutes without talking to each other, and that's really bad !</p>
                <p>To sum up, people should try to keep the social networks in mute when you're with your love one. Do not post anything stupid that can jeoprodise your relationship. Use social network when you're away, not together.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
