<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="42" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the impact of social networks on relationships?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I think that with all those social networks, relationships are more difficult, less private.  Many people tend to show too much privacy on the internet.</p>
                <p>I think it makes us more vulnerable, and sensitive to potential attacks from other users.</p>
                <p>You may think you have a lot of friends because you have 200 &quot;friends&quot; on Facebook.  But how many of them are real friends ?  How many of them do you really meet in the &quot;real life &quot; ?  How many of them would really help you right away if you needed help ?</p>
                <p>I regret that many relationships through social networks are actually very superficial, and not honest or sincere.</p>
                <p>I must admit that I am very happy not to be a teenager anymore right now !</p>
                <p>Social networks have removed me from many of my friends.  We still chat online sometimes, but we do not really take the time to meet in &quot;real life&quot; anymore... It's a shame...</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
