<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="19" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do people who live in the public eye have a right to privacy? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I think they do. Everyone have the right to keep their life private, or at least some of it. Living all the time knowing that people know what you do, what and who you like can be quite exhausting.</p>
                <p>Of course, actors, singers and musicians often live thanks to their audience but that doesn't mean the audience has the right to be aware of their every moves!</p>
                <p>The problem is that people are too curisous. They love to read or hear about drama. That's why tabloid are so popular: people want to read about the last or movie their idol is in, they want to know about their love life, family troubles...</p>
                <p>In my opinion, everyone's private life must be respected. Those people who live in the public eye are humans above all and should be respected, by living a part of their life out of the stage.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
