<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Share a memory of a holiday. Where was it, who went, what happened…?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 60 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Last holliday, in jully , I went in Croatia, with my boyfriend for two weeks</p>
                <p>We travelled by plane and we stayed in a appartment at 500m of the beach and near Dubrovnick. The host was very friendly and we haved a very very nice time here.</p>
                <p>We visited two islands, it was very beautiful and the heater was very hot. We were diving in the ocean, there were a lot of colours fishs. We visited a lot of small city and lovely place like cafta, Mlini and the city of Dubrovnick, a medieval town with a big castle and a lot of lovelies streets. We also ate three time at the restaurant and appreciate freshs fishs directly fished from the ocean. To finish, the last day we layed all the day in the beach near the appartment, it was a really small beach but no one exepted the locales peoples went here. It was a really goof time and I was sad to return in belgium.</p>
                <p>So, this memory of this hollidays is one of the best of my memories of hollidays and I hope to return here one day !</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment">A2 verb errors, B1 vocab and text structure</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
