<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="20" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>You are invited to a friend's birthday. You respond thanking him/her. Suggest some different ways that you can help him/her.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 60 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Hi {name}, Thank you for your invite ! I was so happy te receive it !</p>
                <p>I'm free at this date and if you need some help to prepare this event, il would be glad to come early for helping you. I have some talents for cooking delicious dishes so I can make a cake : chocolate, apples, cheesecake and so on. Anything you want !</p>
                <p>No party without drinking also ! I have good plans to buy alcohol cheaper... Tell me what you want and I can ask it ! Don't forget soda or juice to make some cocktails like Pisang, BloodyMary,... There is a market near of my house where they sell glasses for beerpong ! I'm sure there will be a lot of fun because your friends will be comfortable after drinking !</p>
                <p>At home I have a Wii with the game Dancing : it's so hilarious to see the other people dance weirdly ! The songs go from Mamma Mia to Katy Perry : there is a large choice for any wish.</p>
                <p>Think about presents you want to receive ! Make a list or share some ideas to your friend to be well surprised at your birthday.</p>
                <p>Hope to have some news and see you soon !</p>
                <p>Kisses,</p>
                <p>{name}</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
