<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>In my opinion, everyone wants to reach happiness. That idea is what drives people throughout their lives, what influences them the most when facing important choices. Now, in a world where capitalism has so deeply spreaded in all aspects of the society that wealth became the principle value by which a person can mesure his success and thus, his happiness, grinding money for the sake of it seems like the rational thing to do.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Should {name}, who truly enjoys chess, try to find a chess-related job ? Sure, why not ? But what if this job doesn't provide enough money for her to carry about her future family ? Perhaps she could study chess-related field like mathematics, psychology or computer science and get a job with a bigger salary ?</p>
                <p/>
                <p>At this point, one could easily argue that she might end up burned out and unhappy with her job, but my main argument here is : the best answer to the question stands in both statements. However, this is also a matter of proportion. Indeed, there is a level beyond which salary by itself has less value that happiness.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>To conclude, I think that making money is more important as you are less rich, whilst caring for having an enjoyable job is a privilege of wealthier people.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">C1 word choice and structures, too many B2 vocab and syntax errors.</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
