<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What advice would you give to help improve the environment?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Eco friendly</p>
                <p>Environnment becomes a big challenge in the last decades. It is known currently that we have to change some of our habits because our way pf living is not sustainable in long-term. A lot of negative effects are expected in some countries in the world. It is very important to have a respectfull behaviour in our daily life. Some pieces of advice will be given to adopt an eco friendly behaviour.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>First, I think everybody could make something at his own level. People could take public transportations in place of car to make court travels or to go working. It is aso possible to buy food in cooperatives or bio food to avoid some longs travels around the world which are very pollutives.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Second, some  little habits have to be changed. For instance, it is better to take showers than baths or to use his washmachine during the night, to switch off the ligts when you leave a place. It is little things that seems to be not usefull or not enough but that could have an effect indeed.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Finally, some pieces of advices had been given. Some of them are concerned consumption and other our habits. It is just little things but if everyone take this into account, it could have a big impact.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">Some b2 vocab and structures, b1 tense and syntax errors</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
