<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="22" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>At the moment, there are a lot of student who want to study abroad in their last year of education. Their main reason is to improve their level of a foreign language.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>For this same reason, I think that study abroad be a compulsory part of education. In deed, with it, students improve very fast a foreign language. It is more efficient that learn the language by themselve because they are using it in the real life with people who just speak in the foreign language and so it's faster and easier to learn the language.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>However, I'm not really sure that study abroad be a compulsory part of education for each student. In deed, some study don't need to be accompagned with a foreign language. The natal language could be only necessary. This is the case for example for the psychology, medicine, etc.. Also, I think that if study abroad is an obligation, students will not live it like a reward but more like a punishment. They will not be happy to improve their language and so that could be a very bad experience.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Finally, study abroad be a complusory part of education for the main part of education but it would not be an obligation. I think it's necessary to keep it as a reward for students that want to improve a language.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
