<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="22" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the impact of social networks on relationships?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Well, I guess that social networks allow people to maintain more relationships than before, even though these relationships are less consistent than those in real life. But still, people can get information about &quot;friends&quot; they won't meet again anytime soon. This leads to what we could call a feeling of knowing about these people. In fact, social networks users tend to expose their life, and it allows their contacts to know way more than what they would know if their relationship didn't include social networks.</p>
                <p>But in my opinion, social networks are useful tools to maintain social contacts. You can use them to get in touch with old friends, to invite people to an event of yours in an easier way or to keep tuned about your friends' news in a more efficient way. All you have to do is browse an application or a webpage and in an eyeblink you can get informations that you would have got with a dozen of phone calls and a hundred of texts - or even worse, letters.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">C1 structures, some B2 vocab errors</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
