<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="23" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="de"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the impact of social networks on relationships?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Do, nowadays, our relationships depend on social networks ?</p>
                <p/>
                <p>As everyone knows, social networking is part of our lives and for some of you it is pretty about your life. The world is fully connected, you can find anything anywhere on the Internet. You can also see and talk with people instantly all over the world. You have access to worldwide news and much more information.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>About social networks impacting on our lives, these should be certainly used with moderation, they should not be interfeering with our social life until cutting off our real social life.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If used with wisdom and carefulness, these social networks are very usefull and meaningfull when organization is needed, for example : at the university, everyone can share course notes, information about schedules, etc.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>In conclusion, social networks are really convenient in everyday's life if used correctly and not too frequently. Still keep in mind to have a real social life with friends and family. Do not let technology take over your life.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
