<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do people who live in the public eye have a right to privacy? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Some people argue that choosing the path to celebrity doesn't give you anymore the right to claim some privacy for youself. While I partly agree with that point of view, I tend to think every human being deserves the right to keep some decency and share only the things he or she wants.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>As written in our constitution, everyone should have the right to live his life privately. Nevertheless, some people have chosen to live in the public eye and share their private and most intimate moments with complete strangers. This is a choice they made as responsible adults and there is nothing wrong with it in my view.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>That being said, we have seen too many times these last years celebrities being exposed on the internet by hackers. These hackers have chosen to share private pictures of these celebrities without their consents and this is  something very wrong which proves once again how much our society has driften away from the value of respect we used to share. Being famous doesn't give you the right to disrespect others, so what right do we have to disrespect well-kwnown people?</p>
                <p/>
                <p>In conclusion, I am strongly convinced that each person living on this planet should have some basic rights, that includes a right to privacy. So I don't believe we should blame famous people for keeping some intimate moments to themselves.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">C2 structures, too many syntax and vocab errors for C2.</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
