<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="higher-secondary"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do people who live in the public eye have a right to privacy? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>The right to privacy has never been as important as it is today. Wherever we look, this issue keeps making the front page of every newspaper. The progresses of technology makes it increasingly harder to guarantee it. Among those concerned by the issue, movie stars and VIP's. In this essay, it will be discussed about the right to privacy for those who live in the public eye.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The right to privacy is principle that can be found in every democracy in the world. It is tightly bound to other principles such as freedom of speech, freedom of thaught, secrecy of the vote, etc. It garantees to every citizen the right to live the life he/she choosed to live, without having to face other people's opinions an judgements. That being said, the importance of this right can be easily understood.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>If the right to privacy is considered to be essential for every citizen, there is no reason to think that it could be denied to VIP's just  because their job involves a public part. Besides, fame isn't always a choice, but rather the consequence of a succesfull carreer in a certain area. For instance, a writer agrees to sell a book to a reader, but that doesn't mean he agrees to have every detail of his private life revealed.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">C1 structures and logic, but many  syntax and vocab errors. B2?</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">Some lower level errors.</note>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
