<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="21" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in a university-level language learning classroom</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Eating a balanced diet is the most important factor for a healthy life. Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>It's probably true to say that eating a balanced diet is a key factor for a healthy life.</p>
                <p>Some people may refer to the well known sentence &quot;Mens sana in corpore sano&quot;. Needless to say, the first step to be healthy is to eat well.</p>
                <p>However, I am not sure that a balanced diet is the most important goal to have an healthy life.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Firt of all, diet can very fast become a source of stress when people attach to much importance to it.</p>
                <p>Clearly we all know someone whi is a diet freak.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Secondly, nowadays it is hard to find easily healthy products which are affordable. Indeed, eating good products has a price.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Furthermore, there are many others factors to take into account when we talk about healthy life. I tend to think that sport contributes to have a healthy life as much as a balanced diet.</p>
                <p>I do not mean by this that sport is the most important factor but it sure is essential to be in good shape.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Meanwhile, I am convinced that people who care about eating variate and healthy are more enclined to have a healthy life. Studies have shown that they are often less tired, more motivated, more concentrated and better looking.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>While I accept that eating a balanced diet is very important I feel that there are a lot of orther factors to take into account.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
