<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="56" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Imagine your life in 10 years time. What will it look like?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 60 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>My life in 10 years time will be Happy !!! i hope !!!  I am already Grand-mother of one beautiful and lovely little girl and in a fews weeks , i will be still an happy Grand-mother for the second time !  My life in 10 years time will be happy with my little children !   i will travel around the world like &quot;Marie Popins&quot; for the see my lovely little girls...  Because , i have a american girl , she is born in San-Francisco and  my futur little girl will be born in London ...   i will need many money for to take often the airplane !  My life in 10 years time will be rich of Happinness with my little children ...  it' very enjoy to travel with my husband and with my children ! i like to visit the cities , the landscapes, de countries ...   i like to visit the museums, to eat at the restaurants and to discovery the news musics , the news paintings of the World...  i like also to speak English with the news peoples ...   i like also shopping !! but it is an expensive activity !!!  i hope to keep a good healthy for me and for my all family ...   i will need for ever my family around me ...   My favorite activity is to travel for to see my lovely children and my grandchildren ...  i can also achieve the beautiful things with my grandchildren ... i like painting with them or learning the news things ...  i like the life for ever !!!  As soon !  {name}</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                    <note type="comment">Rep.use of similar sentence structures very common mistakes assoc.with translating</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>A2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
