<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="50" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>If you had 1 million euros, what would you do with it?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 80 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>If I had 1 million euros, I'd like to buy a house in California, USA...</p>
                <p>It would be just enough money to have it, it's soooo expensive over there !</p>
                <p>Since I came back from Cupertino , &quot;Silicon Valley&quot; in 2003 and after leaving  the time of my life with husband and children for 5 years, I'm still nostalgic about the quality of my life I found at that place .</p>
                <p>I spent my time visiting nice places and meet nice people coming from lots of different horizons. I enjoyed the incredible nature and green spaces,  national parks, mountains,  perfect weather,...Whatever people here in Belgium were saying about the bad side of &quot;America&quot;, I was pleased to eat good food, fresh fruits and veggies, excellent meat and fish ! I met thousands of nice people with different cultures.</p>
                <p>My fiction new house would be not as big as the kind that we can see on movies but more the type of a traditional american house with that famous &quot; family room&quot;  with a small garden attached to it in an aerated neighborhood. If I'had 1 million euros ( dollars), I'd work as a teacher in a primary school helping children with disability and of course ....for free !</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">Some B2 ambiguities</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
