<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="56" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I personally think it is more important to have an enjoyable job than to make money.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Of course everybody needs money to live but we don't need to live for money.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>On the other hand, if somebody spends the whole day at work, this has to be pleasant and interesting.  The job itself first and also the colleagues.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>- Through the job first, you may learn a lot of things, new matters for instance, new ways to work.  By working with foreigners (abroad), it makes you openminded.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Working hard may also bring a lot of stress of course</p>
                <p/>
                <p>- Then if you share your time with nice colleagues, this can help you in case the job is less interesting.  You are still happy when you are going to work.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Unfair colleagues cause today of lot of problems (especially psychological ones).</p>
                <p/>
                <p>The dream should be to have both nice colleagues and interesting job but I think this aim is very difficult to achieve.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Unfortunately, there are more and more problems at work and the negative points are taking the upper hand.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>This was a resume of my opinion concerning this matter.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
