<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="24" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>As far as I am concerned, I indeed think that studying abroad should be a compulsory part of education. However when I say &quot;education&quot;, I mean higher school or university. Whatever three or five years, every student should spend at least six months abroad. First and foremost, from a personal point of view, it allows the student to be out of his confort zone which is a essential step in every life. It forces the youth to discover another culture, sometimes even another language, enabling him to come back in his country more open-minded, critical, aware of what happening outside of his borders. From a educational point of view, it makes possible for the student to be conscious about another way of studying. With regard to my experience, I made my university exchange in Peru. There the system was quite different than the Belgian one. Whereas Belgian universities don't give students an ongoing work, the Peruvian requirements were higher along the whole year. I had to work every week which enables me to be ready for the exams whitout being forced to study a lot the week before. For those reasons, studying abroad should be compulsory for everyone as long as it makes you happier.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
