<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="36" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do you think it is more important to have an enjoyable job or to make money? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>I'm an artist. I make comix, silkscreen printing, engraving. So maybe am i a particular kind of people...I always knew i'll never make a lot of money with this sort of life, and maybe i put this idea so deep in my mind that i made an aversion to money winning. I make drawings all the time, and sometimes i make illustrations to have some money, and the artistic process is more difficult in these cases...not because i make it for others,  because there is money at the end...i don't know why... Some people makes thiers jobs to have money, they have no problems with any questions...  after the work, the work is over, they have the money, they have the rest of the day to make other things. For me it never stop, creation is always in my mind, the day  never end, i dream of it, and i don't have money. So what is the best ? I love my work,  it's all my live, and i can't do anything else... And i don't care about the money. Enjoying our work is very important, but it's just a question of priority. There are a lot of jobs really fun where you can make a lot of cash, money is your goal, why not after all ... And there  are a lot of job really fun where you make no cash... but you like it anyway, because you trust in what you do, money is not a goal, you wake up in the morning to make something that makes you happy, and maybe proud. It's a conscience choice...</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">B1 syntax errors and the logic jumps around, B2 vocab with B1 error make/do</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
