<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="53" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Should study abroad be a compulsory part of education? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 100 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>N.B. I did not know the word &quot;compulsory&quot; and I needed to check the translation :)</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Yes, I think that it would be very interesting for each kid and teenager to study abroad at some moments of his scolarity.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>In general and especially in Belgium, be opened to different languages is really important.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Belgium is a trilingual country. But a lot of belgian people are not familiar with the three languages. &quot;False immersion&quot; in a school based in its own village or its own city is quite artificial. And until studying abroad is not compulsory, it would be a kind of leisure for some students.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>So I think that real scholar programmes with immersion already in other regions inside the country and also outside the country would be very profitable for everybody.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>Be opened to foreign languages, other cultures, other mentalities, other uses, other environments is an important part of education, a way to grow up and to understand the world.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>But there is of course a lot of questions. Which budget for the State, which organisation for the school and for the families, ...? Complicated to create that!</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">some B1 vocab, some attempts at B2 structures fail.</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">B1/B2 level.</note>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
