<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="39" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="graduate-doctorate"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do people who live in the public eye have a right to privacy? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>People who live in the public eye certainly do have a right to privacy. This is a fundamental right of all human beings. However, the reality is probably that this right is not respected. For many famous persons, we see too often private pictures or information relative to intimacy published in tabloids. I cannot imagine that stars, politicians, members of royal families, etc. can go out in any public place without the fear of being recognised. If I were them, I would feel that as a violation of my freedom and of one of the most basic human rights. Medias and fans seem to forget that famous people are as human as they are and that they have the same needs, dreams, fears and hopes as anybody else. Yet, there may be some exceptions: some people who actually like to see their whole life becoming public. They may accept to lose their privacy in the name of glory and fame. But I believe that this is rare and that most famous people actually wish to see their right to privacy respected.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                    <note type="comment">One C1 idiom error, one syntax error</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
