<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="87" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do people who live in the public eye have a right to privacy? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Yes they have. If I were a &quot;star&quot; I would enjoy to meet my fans ,</p>
                <p>to shake hands, to hear how fond they are of   marvellous myself.</p>
                <p>Just for a short time though, as I would soon get bored to find reporters</p>
                <p>paparazzis or  excited girls ( this being questionnable... )  ) in my sleepingroom or elsewhere in my house.</p>
                <p>The main problem for such people is how to preserve their privacy should they  want to . Public eye implies public appearance . A  so-called star is not much by itself, it needs a manager , a financial advisor a marketing staff, just name them.</p>
                <p>Main point for me is Morality . How to keep a balanced life among the ones</p>
                <p>who are making a living thanks to me , how to sort the good ones from the others needs a sharp and permanent  control of their job.</p>
                <p>To keep in mind  some ,perhaps many , are jealous and wish me the worst</p>
                <p>could help not  to fall  into what  they want me to.</p>
                <p>This a rather pessimistic comment so far.</p>
                <p>Politicians, artists, stars are  used to meet  or ought to learn how to cope with &quot;the publc eye&quot; . They have power they enjoy high incomes and I agree that many are not  &quot;rotten&quot; nor  morons and deserve a  positive mark.</p>
                <p>I keep my eyes open and go back to my private life that is my wife</p>
                <p>needs me at once. So ,bye,  she is my star and has an eye on me ...</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">B1 syntax and vocab errors. punctuation and paragraphing are B1. B2 verbs and vocab choice</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
