<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="24" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do people who live in the public eye have a right to privacy? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Yes, there should be a separation between private and professionnal life. Even tough a part of some people's job is to be famous, well knowned, and therefore being seen, they should have the right to a private life. The devellopment of their children and their couple relation might be endangered with the omnipresence of photographs and media in their life. They already have to bear this situation at their work or when they show themselves, and it's got to be enough pressure. So let them have a family life without trying to sneak in! Isn't it the first amendement of the constitution to have the right to freedom? And what freedom is greater than the freedom to be forgotten to be eyes of the others, the ones that you do not care about. And this, to be more present to those you love, because real love don't come from a horde of unknowned people! This kind of love is called &quot;admiration&quot; and this is so futile that you can lost all admiration in one time. But you will always get the love you deserve. If you deserve it!</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment">B2 structures</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">B2 vocabulary.  I'm not sure of the argument.</note>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
