<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="37" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="graduate-doctorate"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the impact of social networks on relationships?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Social networks can impact relationships at different levels. First of all, they can serve as upgraded address books that allow people to remain connected even if life has separated them. Social networks also allow people to stay closer as they can stay away while remaining aware of their friend's whereabouts.</p>
                <p>On the other hands, social networks might hinder or slow down the creation of new friendships as, when embedded in a new environment, protagonists might decide to stay connected to their 'old' friends and not open up as fast.</p>
                <p>Also, being connected through social networks might give the false impression of knowing people while what we have access to is only a distilled and strongly editer version of people's lives.</p>
                <p>Lastly, social networks might be able to create relationships which otherwise would physically not have been possible. For example, a young Australian boy living in the Outback whose passion is astronomy might be able to get in touch with a girl from Iran who dreams to become an astronaut.</p>
                <p>Overall, social networks reshape our relationships by altering the distances as we know them and creating a new canvas where the world looks much smaller.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">just 2 mistakes  well developed</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                    <note type="comment">C1 syntax errors, C2 vocab and logic</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                    <note type="comment">Flowing text, but some errors - prepositions, expression, unnecssary &quot;the&quot;&quot;.&quot;</note>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
