<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="25" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Do people who live in the public eye have a right to privacy? Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>My answer to this question is yes, famous people do have a right to privacy. Artists, actors, musicians, politicians (and so on) don't need every single aspects of their life known and shown to the whole world. The only thing that should matter is if these people do their job right. As long as they don't break any rule, why should we know who they married and what their children look like or if they cheated,... Furthermore, media making money by invading privacy are often terrible. Examples of this are tabloids or reality show like the Kardashians. That is not good TV.</p>
                <p/>
                <p>It's getting harder and harder for celebrities to keep their private life private, with the increase of social media and everybody owning a camera phone. We should put ourselves in their shoes and ask us how we would like to be treated if we were in their place.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">The sentence starting with furthermore stops it from being a C2 as it doesn't make sense.</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment">B2? Some s errors (A2)</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>C1</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
