<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="22" role="participant" sex="F">
                    <education type="undergraduate-bachelor"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>What is the impact of social networks on relationships?</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Social networks tends to create a distance between people, but paradoxally it is also a very good way to keep in touch with friends and family abroad.</p>
                <p>I would say that the impact of social network on relationship depend very much on how it is used, that comment is true for most of the new communication technology that are spreading nowadays.</p>
                <p>Considering social network as facebook or instagram, the impact on people's life can be quite important. For the persons who are particularly influencable (such as teenagers for example) seeing too many images of the same kind (thin models, beautiful holiday pictures,...) that reflect a life that is, most of the time, only superficial and unrealistic can be devastating on their self-esteem and the value they give to their lifes. Adults are of course also concern by this impact, especially those who are already experimenting trouble such as depression and self-depreciation.</p>
                <p>On the other hand, social networks are an efficient media for communication, it allows to share things that we would have never shared before, andto anyone arround the globe. The respect of personal privacy is actually an other issue that can be pointed out when we take social networks in consideration, but that fact has less todo with the impact it can have on relationships.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">B2 vocab choice and logic, B1 vocab and syntax errors</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">Reads well, but some significant errors in some vocabulary.</note>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
