<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TEI>
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title/>
                <author>ALTISSIA International s.a.</author>
                <author>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</author>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <distributor>Centre de traitement automatique du langage (CENTAL)</distributor>
                <pubPlace>Louvain-la-Neuve</pubPlace>
                <date>2017</date>
                <availability>
                    <licence target="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/">Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License</licence>
                </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <p/>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
        <profileDesc>
            <particDesc>
                <person age="25" role="participant" sex="M">
                    <education type="graduate-master"/>
                    <langKnowledge>
                        <langKnown level="native" tag="fr"/>
                    </langKnowledge>
                </person>
                <listPerson type="examiners">
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.1"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.2"/>
                    <person role="examiner" sex="F" xml:id="examiner.3"/>
                </listPerson>
            </particDesc>
            <settingDesc>
                <p>collected in an electronic language learning platform</p>
            </settingDesc>
        </profileDesc>
    </teiHeader>
    <text>
        <body>
            <div type="question">
                <p>Eating a balanced diet is the most important factor for a healthy life. Explain your point of view.</p>
                <note type="word-limit">(at least 150 words)</note>
                <label type="level">
                    <span>C2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
            <div type="answer">
                <p>Dear reader, let me share with you a little of what I gain by being schooled at Liège city. Any level of expectation is subject to a scale. In my understanding, unit of measurements have been made and are maintained by humans. In other words, talking about eating a balanced diet as the most important factor for a healthy life, remains what humankind has always been trying to do : compare itself to its ability to tailor its own scale, which should be the best if the wiĺlingness of continious positive improvement exist. The real question is : who is scaling the initial scale in order to keep as long as possible the power of the scale ownership factor  ? ..  Health is like the factor  which has to be closely monitored. Without being healthy any human lost their mind. So to be a good scaler one should absolutely be as healthy as possible. What if life is not understandable at the highest state of consciouness, who will be able to judge weather choices are what is called balanced ? History shows that any species alive deserves what is best for them but jealousness as failed in giving what any species really deserves. Free choices as well as imposed ones are not anymore at stake. What will define the future steps of the evolution process is our ability to learn from history, to live it through experiences, to learn to look ahead and to share. {name}. {name}. {name}. {name}.</p>
            </div>
            <div type="grading">
                <label corresp="#examiner.1" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment"/>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.2" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B1</span>
                    <note type="comment">zero logic. B1 sentence structures exist, and the vocab is b1 to b2</note>
                </label>
                <label corresp="#examiner.3" subtype="writing" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                    <note type="comment">B2 vocabulary, but difficult to make sense of.</note>
                </label>
                <label subtype="majority-vote" type="level">
                    <span>B2</span>
                </label>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>
